<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/rss-feed">
                  <channel><title>Decision Resources Group DRG Biopharma</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/rss-feed</link><description>Documents on Decision Resources Group DRG Biopharma. Accepts optional parameter MaxDays which specifies the maximum age of documents to list.</description><copyright>© 2000 - 2020 DR/Decision Resources, LLC.</copyright><totalpages>18</totalpages><item><title>Vascular Access Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/vascular-access-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The European market for vascular access devices will see slight growth over the forecast period, driven in large part by the rising adoption of&amp;nbsp;PICCs in all European countries, as well as the rising adoption of new technologies such as power-injectable devices, and devices with antimicrobial coatings. However, market revenues will be hindered to some extent by declining&amp;nbsp;ASPs resulting from pricing pressures and increasing competition. Importantly, the impact of the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic on procedures, unit sales, and revenues has been incorporated into the market projections.

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides high-level market metrics for the vascular access device&amp;nbsp;market&amp;nbsp;in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2021/01/07</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Jackie Liu</author><report_nid>903313</report_nid></item><item><title>Trauma Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/trauma-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	Compared to other major orthopedic device markets, the European trauma device market will be somewhat less severely impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic given the urgent nature of many trauma cases. Following the impact of the pandemic, the market will&amp;nbsp;see modest growth through 2029. Financial constraints and the increasing presence of&amp;nbsp;GPOs will, however, contribute to downward&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;pressures, limiting revenue growth to some extent.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for trauma devices in Europe across a 10-year period.

	​
</description><updateddate>2021/01/05</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/06</pubdate><author>Samantha Chow</author><report_nid>902946</report_nid></item><item><title>Dialysis Access Treatment Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/dialysis-access-treatment-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The European market for dialysis access treatment devices is a dynamic market that will grow moderately through 2029, driven by the availability of novel and innovative products. However, market revenues will be hindered to some extent by declining&amp;nbsp;ASPs resulting from pricing pressures, increasing competition and the impact of&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic.

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides high-level market metrics for dialysis access treatment devices&amp;nbsp;in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2021/01/05</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/07</pubdate><author>Bishwjit Ghoshal</author><report_nid>902854</report_nid></item><item><title>Dialysis Access Treatment Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/dialysis-access-treatment-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	The Asia Pacific dialysis access treatment device market will&amp;nbsp;grow modestly&amp;nbsp;through 2029, driven by rising incidence of&amp;nbsp;ESRD&amp;nbsp;due to the aging population, coupled with government initiatives to improve access to dialysis care. However, market growth will be hindered to some extent due to the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic.

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides high-level market metrics for dialysis access treatment devices&amp;nbsp;in Asia Pacific, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of the Asia Pacific region,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2021/01/05</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/06</pubdate><author>Bishwjit Ghoshal</author><report_nid>902753</report_nid></item><item><title>Urological Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/urological-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	Despite the impact of the ongoing&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the Asia Pacific urological device market will continue to&amp;nbsp;expand&amp;nbsp;through 2029 due to growing patient awareness of urological treatments in this region. In particular, rising use of minimally invasive laser treatments for urinary stones and&amp;nbsp;BPH&amp;nbsp;will drive sales in several segments of this market, thus fueling overall market growth. However, the market will be negatively affected in the short term by the global&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic.

	​This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for urological devices in the Asia Pacific region across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2021/01/04</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/06</pubdate><author>Hebri Nandita Mallya</author><report_nid>902506</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	Although it will be negatively impacted in the short term by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the biosurgical agent market in Latin America will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate&amp;nbsp;through 2029, primarily driven by&amp;nbsp;favorable demographics, rising awareness of the clinical benefits of these products on surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for biosurgical agents in Latin America, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of the Latin American region, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2021/01/03</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/04</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>901865</report_nid></item><item><title>Neurovascular Devices | Market Insights | US</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/neurovascular-devices/market-insights/us</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a&amp;nbsp;modest impact on the&amp;nbsp;US&amp;nbsp;market for neurovascular devices in the short term. Once the impact subsides,&amp;nbsp;adoption of innovative devices as well as the ongoing expansion of dedicated infrastructure for neurovascular interventions will drive strong growth through 2029.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for stroke devices in the US&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The US neurovascular&amp;nbsp;device market will be impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic in the short term.

	What factors will contribute to the market decline?

	To what degree will the pandemic affect different procedures and devices?

	How soon will procedure volumes, sales, and revenues recover?

	The thrombectomy device market is seeing strong growth.

	How does the update to treatment guidelines contribute to procedure growth?

	How will the expansion of CSCs impact the market?

	What are the dynamics surrounding the use of aspiration and stent retriever techniques?

	Flow-diverting devices are contributing to growth in the embolization market.

	What devices were recently introduced into the market?

	How will the introduction of new flow-diverting devices affect the competitive dynamics of the segment that was previously monopolized by a single competitor?

	How will adoption of flow-diverting devices impact the&amp;nbsp;neurovascular embolization coil and&amp;nbsp;coiling-assist device markets?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Xi Chen</author><report_nid>899551</report_nid></item><item><title>Transcatheter Embolization and Occlusion Devices | Market Insights | US</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/transcatheter-embolization-and-occlusion-devices/market-insights/us</link><description>
	Following the initial impact of the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the US market for&amp;nbsp;TEO&amp;nbsp;devices will expand at a moderate rate. Market growth will be driven by&amp;nbsp;continual product innovations and the approval of new treatment indications, which will support market expansion throughout the forecast period.

	This&amp;nbsp;Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for&amp;nbsp;TEO&amp;nbsp;devices in the US across a 10-year period.

	The US TEO&amp;nbsp;device market will be impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic in the short term.

	What factors will contribute to the market decline?

	To what degree will the pandemic affect different procedures and devices?

	How soon will procedure volumes, sales, and revenues recover over the forecast period?

	Flow-diverting devices are contributing to growth in the neurovascular embolization market.

	What devices were recently introduced into the market?

	How will the introduction of new flow-diverting devices affect the competitive dynamics of the segment that was previously monopolized by a single competitor?

	How will adoption of flow-diverting devices impact the&amp;nbsp;neurovascular embolization coil and&amp;nbsp;coiling-assist device markets?

	The embolization particle market has seen many mergers and acquisitions.

	What makes this market so dynamic and lucrative?

	What competitive strategies are companies following when engaging in mergers and acquisitions in this space?

	How will these mergers and acquisitions shape competitive dynamics in the US&amp;nbsp;TEO&amp;nbsp;embolization particle markets?

	The PV plug market is dynamic, with new companies and products entering this space.

	How has the competitive landscape changed with the emergence of new competitors and products?

	How will the growing PV plug market impact the PV embolization coil market?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Xi Chen</author><report_nid>900001</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Latin America</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/latin-america</link><description>
	Although it will be negatively impacted in the short term by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the biosurgical agent market in Latin America will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate&amp;nbsp;through 2029, primarily driven by&amp;nbsp;favorable demographics, rising awareness of the clinical benefits of these products on surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for biosurgical agents in the US&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect&amp;nbsp;the Latin America biosurgical agent market.

	Which procedure types will be most strongly impacted by challenges associated with&amp;nbsp;COVID-19?&amp;nbsp;

	How will the impact of the pandemic vary by country?

	At what pace is the biosurgical agent market expected to recover?

	The Latin American market is underpenetrated, and the competitive landscape is highly dynamic.

	Which products will see more rapid adoption, and why?

	What recent changes have occurred in the competitive landscape of this market?

	Economic constraints across Latin America have influenced purchasing decisions among health care facilities.

	Which product segments will be the most influenced by budgetary restrictions?

	How do these challenges affect manufacturer pricing decisions in Latin American countries?

	Surgical procedure volume growth drives use of biosurgical agents in the Latin America region.

	Which surgical specialties contribute most to biosurgical agent revenues in the Latin America region?

	How will declining procedure volumes in certain surgical specialties affect market growth?

	What impact will the expanding use of minimally invasive surgical techniques have on the biosurgical agent market?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>899338</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Oncology Devices | Market Insights | United States</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-oncology-devices/market-insights/united-states</link><description>Despite the short-term challenges posed by the COVID-19 pandemic, the US market for interventional oncology devices will grow modestly through 2029. This will be driven largely by the expanding treatable patient populations, an increasing shift towards higher-priced technologies, and growing physician acceptance of interventional oncology procedures. However, growth in this market will be hindered by mixed clinical data and a lack of reimbursement for newer technologies, which has led to a tempered adoption of interventional oncology devices.

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for interventional oncology devices in the US across a 10-year period.

The COVID-19 pandemic will have short term consequences on the interventional oncology device market.

How will COVID-19 affect procedure volumes for the different segments of the interventional oncology device market?

When will procedure volumes start to recover and at what rate will the recovery occur?

The patient population eligible for interventional oncology procedures supports growth in the ablation device and embolization particle markets.

What are the fastest growing patient populations eligible for interventional oncology treatments?

What is the clinical evidence supporting the use of ablation or embolization procedures for other cancer indications?

New ablation devices and technologies are rising in popularity among interventional oncologists.

What are the advantages and disadvantages of each type of ablation device?

How has the uptake of microwave ablation affected the market for RF ablation devices?

In which indications will these newer ablation devices, such as cryoablation and IRE, experience the fastest adoption?

Growth in the premium-priced embolization particle segments, such as the DEBs and radioembolization sphere spaces, has slowed in recent years.

What factors have contributed to the slowing growth in these markets?

What are challenges facing physicians and competitors in this space?

How has M&amp;amp;A activity shaped the competitive embolization particles market in recent years?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/24</pubdate><author>Kevin Yin</author><report_nid>900295</report_nid></item><item><title>Gynecological Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/gynecological-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	Despite the impact of the ongoing&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, as well as regulatory restrictions surrounding the use of gynecological devices that had been affected by safety-related lawsuits and negative publicity, the Asia Pacific gynecological device market will continue to&amp;nbsp;expand&amp;nbsp;through 2029 due to growing patient awareness of gynecologic treatments in this region. In particular, rising awareness of minimally invasive procedures in China and India, where these techniques have been underpenetrated, will result in increased adoption of associated devices.

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides high-level market metrics for gynecological devices&amp;nbsp;in the Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of the Asia Pacific region,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.​
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Vijjapu Kameswara Rao</author><report_nid>900706</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will negatively impact the European biosurgical agent market in the short term. Once the market stabilizes, the biosurgical agent market in Europe will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate,&amp;nbsp;primarily driven by&amp;nbsp;growing&amp;nbsp;surgical procedure volumes, rising awareness of the benefits of these products in surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications. However, the European market continues to be limited by a lack of reimbursement&amp;nbsp;for biosurgical agents, growing concerns over product cost, and reluctance to use products derived from human tissue among some physicians and patients, hindering the pace of market growth.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for biosurgical agents in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/22</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Nidhi Nagrath</author><report_nid>900480</report_nid></item><item><title>Pain Management Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/pain-management-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The European pain management device market is growing&amp;nbsp;moderately, and will be buoyed over the forecast period by the ongoing launch and growing adoption of non-conservative premium-priced products. Nevertheless, the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will limit growth in the initial years of the forecast period.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for pain management devices&amp;nbsp;in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe, across a 10-year period.&amp;nbsp;
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Dhara Patel, MS Pharm</author><report_nid>897944</report_nid></item><item><title>Breast Implants and Reconstructive Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/breast-implants-and-reconstructive-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The cancellation or postponement of elective procedures, including breast augmentations and reconstructions, due to the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a major negative impact on the European market for breast implants and reconstructive devices in the short term, compounding the recent market decline due to the association of&amp;nbsp;BIA-ALCL&amp;nbsp;with macrotextured silicone breast implants. However, the market will return to growth, supported by continued patient demand for augmentation and reconstruction procedures, innovative technologies that improve the ease of implant placement, and efforts by companies to address concerns regarding product safety.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for breast implants and reconstructive devices&amp;nbsp;in Europe across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Attusa Chikodi</author><report_nid>899213</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Japan</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/japan</link><description>
	Although it will be impacted in the short term by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the biosurgical agent market in Japan will grow at a moderate rate&amp;nbsp;through 2029, driven by rising surgical procedure volumes, the introduction of new products, and expanding indications for the existing products.&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for Biosurgical Agents in Japan&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect&amp;nbsp;the Japanese biosurgical agent market.

	Which surgical specialties&amp;nbsp;will be most impacted?

	At what pace is the biosurgical agent market expected to recover?

	The biosurgical agent market is driven by trends in surgical procedure volumes.

	Which specialties are the strongest drivers of the market and why?

	How will procedure trends be affected by technological advancements in surgical techniques?

	Competitors are expanding their portfolios and investing in clinical trials.

	Which companies lead the market and how are they promoting their products?

	What strategies are used by smaller players to enter the market and compete with existing products?

	Few biosurgical agents are available in the Japanese market.

	Which segments have limited products available and what are the unmet needs?

	Which segments are growing and what are the potential opportunities for market entry?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>898811</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	Following the negative short-term impact of the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the Asia Pacific biosurgical agent market will grow at a modest rate,&amp;nbsp;driven by&amp;nbsp;growing&amp;nbsp;surgical procedure volumes due to expanding aging population and the rising prevalence of diseases associated with aging, obesity, diabetes, and cardi​ovascular disease, in addition to rising awareness of the clinical benefits of these products on surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications. However, growing concerns over product cost and competition from local competitors will limit&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;growth in this market, thus hindering revenue expansion to some extent.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for biosurgical agents in the Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of the Asia Pacific region, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/23</pubdate><author>Hebri Nandita Mallya</author><report_nid>899287</report_nid></item><item><title>Aortic Repair Devices | Market Insights | Canada</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/aortic-repair-devices/market-insights/canada</link><description>
	Following the initial impact of the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the Canadian market for aortic repair devices will expand at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate, driven primarily by endovascular procedure volume growth and&amp;nbsp;continued development and adoption&amp;nbsp;of aortic stent grafts.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for Aortic Repair Devices&amp;nbsp;in Canada across a 10-year period.

	The aortic repair device market will be affected by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;crisis.

	How will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;outbreak affect the aortic repair device market?&amp;nbsp;

	How quickly are procedure volumes expected to recover?

	Aortic repair can be performed using endovascular, surgical or hybrid procedures.

	To what extent are hybrid aortic repair procedures being performed for aortic arch and thoracoabdominal indications in Canada?

	How will off-the-shelf branched devices for the aortic arch effect the Canadian market?

	Which indication has the highest endovascular penetration in Canada?

	How are aneurysms at the iliac-branch treated in Canada?

	Manufacturers in Canada compete for hospital tender contracts

	How has this practice affected the Canadian aortic competitive landscape?

	Which competitors gain the most from this competitive landscape?

	To what degree will price competition to win contracts affect the market overall?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Pulla Siva Kumar</author><report_nid>898644</report_nid></item><item><title>Endoscope Service | Market Insights | United States</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/endoscope-service/market-insights/united-states</link><description>The COVID-19 pandemic will have a significant impact on the US endoscope service market in the short term. Once the market stabilizes, however, the US endoscope service market will expand modestly through 2029, with OEMs continuing to generate the majority of revenues; however, third-party company servicing revenues will grow at a faster rate than those of OEMs, despite the current concerns regarding the possibility of the FDA regulating third-party servicing and the safety concerns surrounding reusable endoscopes.

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for endoscope service in the US across a 10-year period.

The COVID-19 pandemic will affect the US endoscope service market.

To what extent will the COVID-19 pandemic impact the US endoscope service&amp;nbsp;market?

How will the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic differ between segments?

OEMs will generate the vast majority of revenues in the US endoscope service market over the forecast period.

What measures are OEMs taking to maintain and improve their position in the market?

What are the limitations that OEMs are facing in the market?

How does growth vary between OEMs and third-party endoscope servicing companies?

More stringent FDA regulations on third-party servicing of medical devices are expected in the near future.

What are some recent actions the FDA has taken in regard to third-party servicing?

How will the increase in FDA regulation impact the third-party servicing business?

Due to increasing cases of contamination with durable endoscopes, the trend of for single-use endoscopes is increasing in the market.

How will this impact the endoscope servicing market?

How will this affect the strategies of OEMs and third-party companies?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/24</pubdate><author>Hebri Nandita Mallya</author><report_nid>614310</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Europe</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/europe</link><description>
	Although it will be impacted in the short term by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the European biosurgical agent market will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate&amp;nbsp;through 2029, primarily driven by growing surgical procedure volumes, rising awareness of the benefits of these products in surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications. However, the European market continues to be limited by a lack of reimbursement&amp;nbsp;for biosurgical agents, growing concerns over product cost, and reluctance to use products derived from human tissue among some physicians and patients, hindering the pace of market growth.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for biosurgical agents in Europe, with market projections&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect&amp;nbsp;the European biosurgical agents market.

	Which types of&amp;nbsp; surgical specialties will be most impacted?

	How will the impact differ by country?

	At what pace is the biosurgical agent market expected to recover?

	Increasing surgical procedure volumes in Europe will largely dictate the growth of the overall market.

	Which surgical specialties have the largest market size for biosurgical agents?

	How will declining procedure volumes in certain surgical specialties affect market growth?

	Product penetration by surgical specialty will influence overall market trends.

	Which specialty type has seen the highest overall penetration of biosurgical agents?

	Which biosurgical agent materials are most popular and drive unit sales within each specialty?

	Despite cost-containment efforts across European health care systems, biosurgical agent&amp;nbsp;ASPs&amp;nbsp;will not decline significantly.

	How will&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;trends differ by product type and across countries?

	What pricing strategies are companies employing?

	Product innovation and the expansion of approved indications will support market growth.

	What new products are anticipated to enter the market and how will they be received?

	How will new indications impact market growth and surgeon adoption?

	Which companies have obtained expanded approvals for new indications?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/21</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>898945</report_nid></item><item><title>Pain Management Devices | Market Insights | US</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/pain-management-devices/market-insights/us</link><description>
	Expanding patient volumes and a growing focus on non-opioid pain management will drive growth in the US pain management device market over the forecast period, although the market continues to be hindered by reimbursement challenges and pricing pressures. In addition, the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will limit growth in the initial years of the forecast period.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for pain management devices&amp;nbsp;in the US&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will negatively impact the US pain management device market.&amp;nbsp;

	Which types of procedures and device segments will be most impacted?

	At what pace are pain management device markets expected to recover?

	Pain management procedures are increasingly being carried out in alternate care settings.

	How are competitors adjusting their marketing strategies to reflect this trend?

	What factors are influencing the purchasing decisions of pain specialists in alternate care facilities?

	Infusion pain pumps are generating large revenues due to high volumes of cancer and postoperative pain patients.

	What features are facilities prioritizing when they purchase new infusion pumps?

	How are care providers using HCIT functions to improve delivery of infusion pain therapy?

	SCS&amp;nbsp;devices and RF&amp;nbsp;ablation devices are experiencing uptake as late-stage therapies for back pain.

	What factors are driving adoption of these devices?

	What are manufacturers in other back pain treatment device segments are doing to remain competitive?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Sophia Quraishi</author><report_nid>898286</report_nid></item><item><title>Diabetes Care Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/diabetes-care-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>Despite the impact of the global&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the diabetes care device market in the Asia Pacific region will&amp;nbsp;grow moderately&amp;nbsp;over the forecast period, fueled by an expanding diabetic patient population in the Asia Pacific region. However, strong cost constraints&amp;mdash;particularly in China and India&amp;mdash;continue to impede the uptake of premium-priced products, limiting the market to some extent.

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for diabetes care devices in Asia Pacific&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Dhara Patel, MS Pharm</author><report_nid>897848</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Cardiology Devices | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-cardiology-devices/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	Although the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a negative impact on procedure volumes and market growth in 2020, the Latin America market for&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;devices will expand&amp;nbsp;moderately&amp;nbsp;through 2029; driven by an expanding&amp;nbsp;CAD&amp;nbsp;patient pool and increasing adoption of premium-priced devices&amp;mdash;such as next generation&amp;nbsp;DES&amp;nbsp;and intravascular imaging catheters and pressure&amp;nbsp;guidewires&amp;mdash;supporting revenues. However, continuing budgetary constraints among Latin American facilities will inhibit uptake of high-cost products and limit overall market growth.&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for interventional cardiology devices in Argentina, Brazil, Colombia, and Mexico across a 10-year period.&amp;nbsp;
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/21</pubdate><author>Sangeetha Iyer</author><report_nid>897158</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Oncology Devices | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-oncology-devices/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	Although the Latin American interventional oncology device market will be hindered in the immediate term by the impact of the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the market will resume&amp;nbsp;moderate growth&amp;nbsp;once the market recovers, driven by an increasing patient population, adoption of premium-priced devices, and the introduction of new devices in the countries covered. However, cost constraints in the region&amp;#39;s publicly funded health care systems will limit the pace of revenue expansion.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for interventional oncology&amp;nbsp;devices in the Latin American region,&amp;nbsp;including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Latin America,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/22</pubdate><author>Bishwjit Ghoshal</author><report_nid>898017</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Cardiology Devices | Market Insights | Latin America</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-cardiology-devices/market-insights/latin-america</link><description>Although the COVID-19 pandemic will have a negative impact on procedure volumes and market growth in 2020, the Latin America market for IC devices will expand moderately through 2029; driven by an expanding CAD patient pool and increasing adoption of premium-priced devices&amp;mdash;such as next generation DES and intravascular imaging catheters and pressure guidewires&amp;mdash;supporting revenues. However, continuing budgetary constraints among Latin American facilities will inhibit uptake of high-cost products and limit overall market growth.

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for interventional cardiology devices in Argentina, Brazil, Colombia, and Mexico across a 10-year period.

The Latin America IC device market will be impacted by the COVID-19 pandemic in the early years of the forecast. 

What guidance or recommendations have been issued for IC procedures in the face of infection containment and self-isolation measures?

How will the pandemic impact clinical trials and product launches?

The Latin American market is dominated by international competitors.

What strategies are used by international competitors to succeed in this market?

What is the role of distributors in the success of international companies?

What strategies can new competitors employ to gain entry into the Latin American coronary stent market?

Device ASP trends will play a significant role in determining market growth through 2029.

How will ASP trends vary by country? What factors will contribute to these differences?

How will government-driven pricing pressures and increasing competition affect ASPs, and which product segments will be most impacted?

Adoption of some premium-priced products, such as DCBs and BRS, will be limited through 2029.

How will clinical trial results impact uptake of BRS devices by country?

What factors will limit adoption of premium-priced DCBs?

How are these technologies likely to evolve over the coming years?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Sangeetha Iyer</author><report_nid>896714</report_nid></item><item><title>Pulmonology Devices | Market Insights | US</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/pulmonology-devices/market-insights/us</link><description>
	​In 2020, the&amp;nbsp;US pulmonology device&amp;nbsp;market will be moderately impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic but will nevertheless&amp;nbsp;grow&amp;nbsp;over the forecast period,&amp;nbsp;fueled by bronchoscopy procedure volume growth, favorable demographic trends, and the adoption of premium-priced technologies, particularly in the bronchoscope market. However, a lack of product innovation and minimal procedure volume growth in some pulmonology device market segments will limit the growth of the overall pulmonology device market.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for pulmonology devices in the US across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect the&amp;nbsp;pulmonology&amp;nbsp;device market.

	To what extent will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic impact the&amp;nbsp;pulmonology device market in the US?

	Which device segment will be the most severely impacted by&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic?

	The US pulmonology device market will grow modestly&amp;nbsp;through 2027.&amp;nbsp;

	Which device segments are seeing the strongest growth?

	What types of procedures are driving growth in the US pulmonology device market?

	Despite&amp;nbsp;moderate growth&amp;nbsp;in the overall market, which device segments will decline in size?

	Bronchoscopy procedure volumes continue to rise.&amp;nbsp;

	Which bronchoscopy procedure types will see the greatest growth through 2027?

	What is driving this growth in procedure volumes?

	Which bronchoscopy procedure types are plateauing in growth?

	&amp;nbsp;A number of products have been launched or FDA approved across the pulmonology device market in recent years.

	Which market segments are seeing the most product launches and FDA approvals?

	Which companies have been more active in recent years in coming out with new products?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/21</pubdate><author>Sha Guan</author><report_nid>898103</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | Asia Pacific</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/asia-pacific</link><description>
	Following the negative short-term impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, the Asia Pacific biosurgical agent market will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate, driven by&amp;nbsp;growing&amp;nbsp;surgical procedure volumes due to the expanding aging population and the rising prevalence of diseases associated with aging, obesity, diabetes, and cardiovascular disease. However, growing concerns over product cost and competition from local competitors will limit&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;growth in this market, hindering revenue expansion to some extent.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for biosurgical agents in the Asia Pacific region across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect&amp;nbsp;the Asia Pacific biosurgical agent market.

	Which procedure types will be most strongly impacted by challenges associated with&amp;nbsp;COVID-19?&amp;nbsp;

	How will the impact of the pandemic vary by country?

	At what pace is the biosurgical agent market expected to recover?

	Surgical procedure volume growth drives use of biosurgical agents in the Asia Pacific region.

	Which surgical specialties contribute most to biosurgical agent revenues in the Asia Pacific region?

	How will declining procedure volumes in certain surgical specialties affect market growth?

	What impact will the expanding use of minimally invasive surgical techniques have on the biosurgical agent market?

	In some Asia Pacific countries the use of biosurgical agents is influenced by&amp;nbsp;cultural&amp;nbsp;differences&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;region.

	What strategies are competitors using to promote product sales amid cultural aversion in&amp;nbsp;the region?&amp;nbsp;

	For which biosurgical agents will cultural differences negatively impact unit sales?&amp;nbsp;

	Compared to the US and Europe, the market for biosurgical agents in Asia Pacific countries remains underpenetrated; however competitors are targeting this region because of its growth potential.

	What strategies are competitors using to target the Asia Pacific biosurgical agent market?&amp;nbsp;

	What types of challenges will companies face in this space, and what will they need to do to overcome these difficulties?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/21</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>897642</report_nid></item><item><title>Biosurgical Agents | Market Insights | US</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/biosurgical-agents/market-insights/us</link><description>
	Although it will be impacted in the short term by the COVID-19 pandemic, the biosurgical agent market in the US will grow at a&amp;nbsp;modest rate&amp;nbsp;through 2029, primarily driven by&amp;nbsp;growing&amp;nbsp;surgical procedure volumes, rising awareness of the clinical benefits of these products on surgical outcomes, and the introduction of new products with enhanced features and expanded indications. However, growing concerns over product cost will limit&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;growth in this market, thus hindering revenue expansion to some extent.&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for biosurgical agents in the US&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect&amp;nbsp;the US biosurgical agent market.

	Which surgical specialties will be most impacted?

	At what pace is the biosurgical agent market expected to recover?

	Increasing surgical procedure volumes in the US will largely dictate the growth of the overall market.

	Which surgical specialties have the largest market size for biosurgical agents?

	How will declining procedure volumes in certain surgical specialties affect market growth?

	Product penetration by surgical specialty will influence overall market trends.

	Which specialty type has seen the highest overall penetration of biosurgical agents?

	Which biosurgical agent materials are most popular and drive unit sales within each specialty?

	What product type accounts for the largest portion of the overall market?

	Which product types will exhibit the greatest market growth and why?

	Product innovation and the expansion of approved indications will support market growth.

	What new products are anticipated to enter the market and how will they be received?

	How will new indications impact market growth and surgeon adoption?

	Which companies have obtained expanded approvals for new indications?

	Beyond product innovation and expanding the approved indications of their products, what competitive strategies are vendors prioritizing in this space?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/20</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/21</pubdate><author>Sumit Jain</author><report_nid>897226</report_nid></item><item><title>Spinal Implants | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/spinal-implants/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	While the COVID-19 pandemic will significantly impact the spinal implant market in the short term, favorable demographics and increased access to health care in some of the countries covered will ultimately lead to growth in the Asia Pacific spinal implant market through 2029. Although the spinal implant market will be somewhat limited by pricing pressures, challenging reimbursement environments, and protectionist policies, advancements in medical facilities and an increased focus on physician training will supprt overall market expansion.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for spinal implants&amp;nbsp;in the Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Asia Pacific region, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/17</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/19</pubdate><author>Attusa Chikodi</author><report_nid>896593</report_nid></item><item><title>Electrophysiology Mapping and Ablation Devices | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/electrophysiology-mapping-and-ablation-devices/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The European market for&amp;nbsp;EP&amp;nbsp;mapping and ablation devices will experience moderate growth through 2029, largely as a result of increasing ablation volumes and the use of premium-priced devices in&amp;nbsp;AF treatments. Growth will be hindered to some extent in 2020 due to the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, resulting in delayed procedures for&amp;nbsp;EP&amp;nbsp;and ablation.

	This&amp;nbsp;Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides key market metrics for the EP mapping and ablation device market in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/17</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/18</pubdate><author>Suraj Nair</author><report_nid>896949</report_nid></item><item><title>Gastrointestinal Endoscopy Devices | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/gastrointestinal-endoscopy-devices/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will negatively impact the Latin American&amp;nbsp;GI&amp;nbsp;endoscopy device market. Once the market stabilizes, it will grow modestly during the forecast period because of the improving access to healthcare across the region and the concerted efforts of health systems to implement extensive screening programs, especially for&amp;nbsp;CRC. Having said that, the unstable economic conditions in the region, as well as the practice of reusing&amp;nbsp;GI endoscopy devices among health care facilities, will act as limiting factors for the market.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for the&amp;nbsp;GI&amp;nbsp;endoscopy device market&amp;nbsp;in&amp;nbsp;Latin America,&amp;nbsp;including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Latin America, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/17</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Nidhi Nagrath</author><report_nid>896267</report_nid></item><item><title>Cardiac Assist Devices | Market Insights | United States</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/cardiac-assist-devices/market-insights/united-states</link><description>
	The US market for cardiac assist devices will grow rapidly over the forecast period, fueled by expanding use of cardiac assist devices into an undertreated patient population, particularly in the temporary VAD market. However, the US cardiac assist device market will be impacted to some extent by the COVID-19 pandemic,&amp;nbsp;resulting in some lost procedure volumes in the short term followed by a period of recovery.&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for cardiac assist devices&amp;nbsp;in the US&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The US cardiac assist device market will be affected by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;crisis.

	How will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19 pandemic affect the cardiac assist device market?&amp;nbsp;

	Which market segments will be the most impacted in 2020, and why?

	How have companies responded to the obstacles presented by the pandemic?

	The VAD market will be the strongest driver of growth in the overall cardiac assist device market.

	Which type of VAD&amp;mdash;durable or temporary&amp;mdash;will generate the most revenues throughout the forecast period?

	What are the drivers for growth within the VAD market as a whole, and how do these drivers differ based on VAD durability?

	What impact will new technologies in the durable VAD market have throughout the forecast period?

	What impact will new competitors in the temporary VAD market have throughout the forecast period?

	IABPs were widely used in the US in 2019&amp;nbsp;for the treatment of AHF.

	How will the adoption of temporary VADs affect the IABP market throughout the forecast period?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/17</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/18</pubdate><author>Drew Wallace</author><report_nid>897011</report_nid></item><item><title>Electrophysiology Mapping and Ablation Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/electrophysiology-mapping-and-ablation-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	Growing&amp;nbsp;AF&amp;nbsp;treatment volumes, driven by an expanding patient pool, rising awareness of ablation procedures, and improving access to health care, will fuel strong growth in the Asia Pacific&amp;nbsp;EP&amp;nbsp;mapping and ablation device market through 2029. Growth will be hindered to some extent in 2020 due to the COVID-19 pandemic, resulting in delayed procedures for EP and ablation.

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides key market metrics for EP&amp;nbsp;mapping and ablation devices&amp;nbsp;in the&amp;nbsp;Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Asia Pacific,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/17</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/18</pubdate><author>Suraj Nair</author><report_nid>896659</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Cardiology Devices | Market Insights | Middle East and South Africa (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-cardiology-devices/market-insights/middle-east-and-south-africa-supplemental</link><description>
	Although the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a negative impact on procedure volumes and market growth in 2020, the&amp;nbsp;MESA&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;device market will&amp;nbsp;grow modestly&amp;nbsp;through 2029, driven by the rising prevalence of&amp;nbsp;CAD, expanding penetration of&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;procedures, increasing health insurance coverage in some segments, and government initiatives to improve the accessibility and affordability of&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;devices.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;devices in the&amp;nbsp;MESA&amp;nbsp;region across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Sangeetha Iyer</author><report_nid>894928</report_nid></item><item><title>Vascular Access Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/vascular-access-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific</link><description>
	The Asia Pacific vascular access device market will grow moderately through 2029, driven by an expanding patient population and increasing adoption of premium-priced devices. The COVID-19 pandemic will have an impact on the overall procedure volumes in 2020 with a rebound expected in late 2020 and 2021.

	This&amp;nbsp;Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for vascular access&amp;nbsp;devices in the Asia Pacific&amp;nbsp;countries across a 10-year period.

	Despite increasing failure rates and complications requiring reinsertion, short PIVC&amp;nbsp;insertions continue to be one of the most common invasive procedures in the region.

	What are the current clinical recommendations to reduce PIVC failure?

	What are some of the measures taken by companies to improve PIVC insertion outcomes?&amp;nbsp;

	How will initiatives to educate nurses on PIVC insertion impact the unit sales of short PIVC?

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;global pandemic will have a dual effect on the vascular access market in the short term.

	How will trends change in different vascular access&amp;nbsp;device segments as a consequence of&amp;nbsp;COVID-19 pandemic?&amp;nbsp;

	What factors contribute to the market changes?

	How quickly are procedure volumes expected to recover?

	What plans are being executed by manufacturers in response to the pandemic?

	Increasing incidence of CLABSI with CVC is resulting in a shift toward PICCs. 

	How is the rising adoption of PICCs impacting the sales of CVC units? How does this vary across the Asia Pacific countries?

	What are the marketing strategies adopted by companies to promote PICC sales?

	What are some of the clinical practices initiated to reduce CLABSI with CVCs? How will this impact the CVC market?

	How will the markets for tunneled&amp;nbsp;CVCs and antimicrobial devices perform through 2027?

	Home care therapy continues to grow in most Asia Pacific countries.

	What are some of the vascular access device markets likely to be impacted by the increasing adoption of home care therapy?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Suraj Nair</author><report_nid>895444</report_nid></item><item><title>Laparoscopic Devices | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/laparoscopic-devices/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic and poor economic conditions will have a significant impact on the Latin American laparoscopic device market. Once the market stabilizes, however, it will&amp;nbsp;expand&amp;nbsp;moderately&amp;nbsp;through 2029, driven by an expanding patient base and growth in laparoscopic procedure volumes. Although the poor economic conditions in Latin America continue to create downward pricing pressures and hinder the adoption of premium-priced products such as advanced energy devices, the Latin American laparoscopic device market will expand modestly through 2029, driven by the rise in patient base and growth in laparoscopic procedure volumes.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for laparoscopic devices&amp;nbsp;in Latin America&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/19</pubdate><author>Muskan Kishore</author><report_nid>896050</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Oncology Devices | Market Insights | Latin America </title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-oncology-devices/market-insights/latin-america</link><description>
	Although the Latin American interventional oncology device market will be hindered in the immediate term by the impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, the market will resume&amp;nbsp;moderate growth&amp;nbsp;once the market recovers, driven by an increasing patient population, adoption of premium-priced devices, and the introduction of new devices in the countries covered. However, cost constraints in the region&amp;#39;s publicly funded health care systems will limit the pace of revenue expansion.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for interventional oncology devices in Latin America across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect the interventional oncology device market in the short term.

	How will&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;affect procedure volumes?

	What impact will the pandemic have on market dynamics?

	The ablation device market is dominated by RF ablation, however, new technologies are making their way in the market and will cannibalize the RF ablation device market in the forecast period

	What are the advantages and disadvantages of each type of ablation device offered by competitors and how do these differences affect adoption for different indications?

	What is the current status of device availability in the geographies covered?

	Radioembolization spheres continue to represent the&amp;nbsp;largest&amp;nbsp;segment of the embolization particle market, although the microsphere and&amp;nbsp;DEB&amp;nbsp;markets will also experience growth over the forecast period.

	How will outcomes of trials like SIRFLOX and FOXFIRE affect the adoption and usage of radioembolization spheres?

	What factors are contributing to the growth of the Latin American microsphere and&amp;nbsp;DEB&amp;nbsp;markets?

	The launch of new products will drive the growth of Latin American interventional oncology device market

	What new products are anticipated to be launched in Latin America?

	What product features are companies focusing on during novel product development?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Bishwjit Ghoshal</author><report_nid>895219</report_nid></item><item><title>Interventional Cardiology Devices | Market Insights | Middle East and South Africa</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/interventional-cardiology-devices/market-insights/middle-east-and-south-africa</link><description>
	Although the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a negative impact on procedure volumes and market growth in 2020, the&amp;nbsp;MESA&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;device market will&amp;nbsp;grow modestly&amp;nbsp;through 2029, driven by the rising prevalence of&amp;nbsp;CAD, expanding penetration of&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;procedures, increasing health insurance coverage in some segments, and government initiatives to improve the accessibility and affordability of&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;devices.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for IC&amp;nbsp;devices in the MESA&amp;nbsp;region across a 10-year period.

	The MESA&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;device market will be impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic in the early years of the&amp;nbsp;forecast period.

	What guidance or recommendations have been issued for&amp;nbsp;IC&amp;nbsp;procedures in the face of infection containment and self-isolation measures?

	How will the pandemic impact clinical trials and product launches?

	Several emerging devices that are about to be launched in the US or European market will likely enter the&amp;nbsp;MESA&amp;nbsp;market in the coming years.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;

	Which devices are anticipated to enter the&amp;nbsp;MESA&amp;nbsp;market over the forecast period?

	How will the availability of these new devices impact the overall market?

	The implementation of new medical device regulations in Turkey will result in more stringent regulatory requirements.

	How are competitors expected to respond to the regulations and how will this affect small- and mid-sized emerging competitors in particular?

	Will these regulations impact product launches and product improvements?

	In several Middle Eastern countries, the PTCA Balloon catheter market&amp;nbsp;will be significantly affected by device reuse.

	In which countries is device reuse more prevalent? How will this trend affect unit sales and revenues?

	How will this trend change going forward?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Sangeetha Iyer</author><report_nid>893987</report_nid></item><item><title>Cardiac Assist Devices | Market Insights | Europe</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/cardiac-assist-devices/market-insights/europe</link><description>
	Following the initial impact of the COVID-19 pandemic, the European cardiac assist device market will grow moderately over the forecast period, driven by strong sales in the VAD market; new device launches in the pVAD segment in particular will fuel rapid adoption of temporary VADs.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for cardiac assist devices&amp;nbsp;in Europe&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;cardiac assist device market will be affected by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;crisis.

	How will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;outbreak affect the cardiac assist device market?&amp;nbsp;

	Which market segments will be the most impacted in 2020, and why?

	The introduction of&amp;nbsp;MDR&amp;nbsp;in Europe will result in more stringent regulatory requirements.

	What changes under the&amp;nbsp;MDR&amp;nbsp;will affect the cardiac assist device&amp;nbsp;market?

	How will this impact small and mid-sized emerging companies in the cardiac assist device&amp;nbsp;market?

	The VAD market will be the key driver of the overall cardiac assist device market.

	Which type of VAD will be more rapidly adopted and generate the most revenue through 2029?

	Is the shift from open surgery to percutaneous VADs is moving completely in the various European countries? Why?

	What are the specific limiters for the VAD market in the various European countries?

	The TAH market will see the strongest growth through 2029.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;

	What are the major barriers to&amp;nbsp;TAH adoption, and how will this change going forward?

	What the current drawbacks associated with&amp;nbsp;TAHs, and what is being done to remedy these issues?

	IABPs were widely used in Europe for the treatment of&amp;nbsp;AHF in 2019.

	What factors have led to the substantial usage of&amp;nbsp;IABPs in AHF cases?

	What is limiting the market for IABPs in Germany? Why?

	How will the adoption of temporary&amp;nbsp;VADs affect the&amp;nbsp;IABP&amp;nbsp;system market through 2029?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/18</pubdate><author>Pulla Siva Kumar</author><report_nid>895873</report_nid></item><item><title>Laparoscopic Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/laparoscopic-devices/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a significant impact on the Asia Pacific laparoscopic device market. Once the market stabilizes, however, it will&amp;nbsp;grow moderately&amp;nbsp;during the forecast period. The emerging markets will be driven primarily by rising procedure volumes, while revenue growth in the developed markets will be the result of adoption of advanced products, particularly in the advanced energy device, internal closure device, and laparoscope segments.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for laparoscopic devices in the Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Asia Pacific, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/21</pubdate><author>Muskan Kishore</author><report_nid>896447</report_nid></item><item><title>Aesthetic Injectables | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/aesthetic-injectables/market-insights/asia-pacific-supplemental</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a significant impact on the Asia Pacific aesthetic injectable market in the short term. Once the market stabilizes, however, the market will show strong growth. This growth will be primarily attributed to the rising adoption of aesthetic procedures in the underpenetrated Asia Pacific markets. Increasing aesthetic consciousness, growing urban populations with high disposable incomes, and the overall cost effectiveness of these procedures over surgical options are going to be the major drivers in these markets.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides key market metrics for aesthetic injectables in the Asia Pacific region, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Asia Pacific region, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Raghav Tangri</author><report_nid>896190</report_nid></item><item><title>Therapeutic Botulinum Toxin | Market Insights | Global</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/therapeutic-botulinum-toxin/market-insights/global</link><description>
	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will have a negative short-term effect on the global therapeutic&amp;nbsp;BTX&amp;nbsp;market. The deferral of nonurgent procedures, compounded with economic uncertainty across the globe will hinder procedure volumes and therefore impede market growth. Beyond the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic, the global therapeutic&amp;nbsp;BTX&amp;nbsp;market will grow strongly through 2029, with newly approved indications, the need for repeat&amp;nbsp;BTX&amp;nbsp;treatments, and a largely favorable reimbursement environment driving significant procedure volume and unit sales expansion.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for therapeutic BTX in the US, France, Germany, Italy, Spain, the UK, Japan and Australia across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will hinder growth of the global therapeutic BTX market in the near-term.​

	To what extent will&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;impact the therapeutic BTX&amp;nbsp;market globally?

	Which geographies have experienced the largest impact, and how quickly are procedure volumes expected to recover?

	How are&amp;nbsp;manufacturers preparing for&amp;nbsp;the postpandemic environment?

	New indication approvals and existing indication expansions will be significant drivers in the therapeutic BTX market.

	Which indications contribute the most to growth?

	What regional differences exist regarding indication approvals?

	What new indications have the largest market potential?

	The global therapeutic markets are becoming more and more consolidated.

	What are some key competitive strategies being employed to succeed in the market?

	How do the competitive landscapes differ by region, and what considerations must companies make in particular markets?

	Markets vary greatly by region in terms of size and growth,&amp;nbsp;with the US market experiencing the fastest growth globally.

	What key drivers contribute to a market&amp;#39;s relative size and growth?

	What factors most significantly affect pricing within markets?

	&amp;nbsp;

	Ongoing clinical trials and emerging products&amp;nbsp;could have a significant impact on the BTX market in the future.

	&amp;nbsp;Which clinical trials have been successful and will have significant impact on the market?

	Will emerging products expand on or compete against the existing BTX market?

	What are some potential competitive advantages emerging products might have?

	How will alternative treatments impact the BTX market?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Diwakar Bahuguna</author><report_nid>895691</report_nid></item><item><title>Diabetes Care Devices | Market Insights | Europe | 2019</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/report-library/m360dm0012/diabetes-care-devices-market-insights-europe-2019</link><description>Growth&amp;nbsp;in the European diabetes care device market over the forecast period will be fueled by the rapidly growing&amp;nbsp;diabetes patient population in the region and by a number of new product launches that will generate significant market revenues. The opportunities presented in the diabetes care device market are encouraging companies to invest in R&amp;amp;D and to partner with digital technology companies to develop new products that provide improvements for patients.

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for diabetes care devices in Europe across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/16</pubdate><author/><report_nid>894717</report_nid></item><item><title>Trauma Devices | Market Insights | Europe | 2019</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/report-library/m360tr0055/trauma-devices-market-insights-europe-2019</link><description>The European trauma device market will see modest growth through 2027. Financial constraints and the increasing presence of&amp;nbsp;GPOs will, however, contribute to downward&amp;nbsp;ASP&amp;nbsp;pressures, limiting revenue growth to some extent.&amp;nbsp;

This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for trauma devices in Europe across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/16</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/16</pubdate><author/><report_nid>894232</report_nid></item><item><title>Diabetes Care Devices | Market Insights | United States</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/diabetes-care-devices/market-insights/united-states</link><description>
	​In 2020, the US diabetes care devices market will be moderately impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic but will nevertheless still grow&amp;nbsp;strongly through 2029, fueled by an expanding diabetes patient population in the country, the launch of new and innovative products, as well as the adoption of premium-priced technologies, particularly in the insulin pumps market.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for diabetes care devices in the US across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect the&amp;nbsp;diabetes care&amp;nbsp;device market.

	To what extent will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic impact the&amp;nbsp;diabetes care device market in the US?

	Which device segment will be the most severely impacted by&amp;nbsp;COVID-19 pandemic?

	The US diabetes care device market will grow strongly through 2029.

	How does growth vary between product segments?

	What are the factors driving the market expansion?

	Numerous new competitors are expected to enter this space within the forecast period.

	Who are these competitors and what products are they bringing to the market?

	Which segments are seeing the most incoming competitors?

	Several products within the diabetes care device space have gained Medicare coverage in recent years.

	Which products and companies have benefited from this?

	What other companies are also seeking to gain approval for coverage of their product from CMS?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/18</pubdate><author>Sha Guan</author><report_nid>894580</report_nid></item><item><title>Aesthetic Injectables | Market Insights | Latin America (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/aesthetic-injectables/market-insights/latin-america-supplemental</link><description>
	The Latin American aesthetic injectable market will be negatively affected by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic in the short term.&amp;nbsp;Once the situation improves, however, the market will resume&amp;nbsp;strong growth through 2029, driven by an expanding patient pool, as well as major M&amp;amp;As in the aesthetics space.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for aesthetic injectables in Latin America, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Latin America, across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2021/01/08</pubdate><author>Meenu Sankar</author><report_nid>893893</report_nid></item><item><title>Spinal Implants | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/spinal-implants/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	While the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will significantly impact the market in the short term, other factors, such as relatively high spending on health care and physician training, a growing elderly population, and improving health care access in rural regions will lead to&amp;nbsp;modest growth in the&amp;nbsp;European spinal implant market through 2029. However, downward pricing pressure resulting from hospital budget constraints and implant commoditization will limit overall market potential, even as favorable demographic trends support modest procedure volume growth.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides high-level market metrics for the spinal implant market in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe, across a 10-year period.

	​
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Swarnadip Dutta</author><report_nid>894987</report_nid></item><item><title>Trauma Devices | Market Insights | Europe</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/trauma-devices/market-insights/europe</link><description>
	Compared to other major orthopedic device markets, the European trauma device market will be somewhat less severely impacted by the COVID-19 pandemic given the urgent nature of many trauma cases. Following the impact of the pandemic, the market will&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;see modest growth through 2029. Financial constraints and the increasing presence of GPOs will, however, contribute to downward ASP pressures, limiting revenue growth to some extent.&amp;nbsp;

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for trauma devices in Europe across a 10-year period.

	The COVID-19 pandemic will affect the trauma device market.

	To what extent will COVID-19 impact the European trauma device market?

	How quickly are procedure volumes expected to recover?

	Several manufacturers have recently expanded their product portfolios with the introduction of new devices or&amp;nbsp;by acquiring companies with complementary products.

	Which competitors are using the breadth of their product portfolios to secure&amp;nbsp;trauma device market shares?

	Which companies have expanded their offerings?

	Which segments are seeing increased interest from competitors, and why?

	The European trauma device market will continue to grow through 2029.

	Which product segments will see the greatest increases in unit volumes through 2029, and why?

	Which device segments are seeing revenue declines, and what is contributing to this?

	How are procedural trends shifting due to improved technology and clinical data?

	Rising awareness among patients and increased surgical training will drive demand for patient-specific implants; however, uptake of premium-priced products will be somewhat restricted by hospital budget constraints.

	Which type of premium and patient-specific devices will continue to display revenue growth despite these pressures?&amp;nbsp;

	Which countries will face the greatest pricing pressure?

	How will the adoption of premium-priced products affect sales in competing product segments?

	The introduction of the new MDR will lead to consolidation in some segments of the European trauma device market.

	Which segments and manufacturers will be most affected by the new MDR?

	How will competitors leverage the MDR to their advantage?​
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Samantha Chow</author><report_nid>894263</report_nid></item><item><title>Diabetes Care Devices | Market Insights | Europe</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/diabetes-care-devices/market-insights/europe</link><description>
	​In 2020, the European diabetes care device market will be moderately impacted by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic but will nevertheless grow over the forecast period, fueled by the growing&amp;nbsp;diabetes patient population in the region and by a number of new product launches that will generate significant market revenues. The opportunities presented in the diabetes care device market are encouraging companies to invest in R&amp;amp;D and to partner with digital technology companies to develop new products that provide treatment improvements for patients.

	This Medtech 360 Report provides comprehensive data and analysis on the current state of the market for diabetes care devices in Europe across a 10-year period.

	The&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic will affect the diabetes care device market.

	To what extent will the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic impact the&amp;nbsp;diabetes care device market in Europe? How will the impact vary by country?

	Which device segment will be the most severely impacted by&amp;nbsp;COVID-19?

	There is a great deal of innovation in the European diabetes care market, including the launch of the first&amp;nbsp;hybrid&amp;nbsp;closed-loop &amp;quot;artificial pancreas.&amp;quot;

	Which markets will be the most impacted by new technology, and how will these innovations affect market trends?

	Which new products are in development and when are they likely to enter the market?

	The insulin delivery device market is large&amp;nbsp;and will&amp;nbsp;continue to expand rapidly.

	What factors are driving growth in this market?

	Which types of devices are seeing the strongest adoption, and how are these trends affecting other product segments?

	Product preferences vary significantly by country.

	How is reimbursement affecting product adoption in each country and in what markets is reimbursement expected to change?
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/17</pubdate><author>Sha Guan</author><report_nid>894718</report_nid></item><item><title>Gastrointestinal Endoscopy Devices | Market Insights | Asia Pacific (Supplemental) | 2020</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/report-library/m360gi0040/gastrointestinal-endoscopy-devices-market-insights-asia-pacific-supplemental-2020</link><description>The Asia Pacific&amp;nbsp;GI&amp;nbsp;endoscopy device market will&amp;nbsp;expand quickly&amp;nbsp;through 2028, primarily driven by the&amp;nbsp;growth&amp;nbsp;of underpenetrated endoscopy procedure volumes as more physicians become trained in endoscopic techniques, and as the Chinese and Indian populations gain greater access to health care in their respective markets. The introduction of robotics in gastrointestinal endoscopy will further improve the scope of market growth over the forecast period.

This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides key market metrics for the&amp;nbsp;GI&amp;nbsp;endoscopy device market&amp;nbsp;in the Asia Pacific region,&amp;nbsp;including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Asia Pacific,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/15</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/15</pubdate><author/><report_nid>893715</report_nid></item><item><title>Dental Implants | Market Insights | Europe (Supplemental)</title><link>https://insights.decisionresourcesgroup.com/device/dental-implants/market-insights/europe-supplemental</link><description>
	The European dental implant market will be hindered by the&amp;nbsp;COVID-19&amp;nbsp;pandemic in the short term. However, once the impact subsides, the market will see modest growth throughout the forecast period driven by growing awareness of the benefits of dental implant surgery and more trained physicians. Although stringent regulations and economic constraints in some countries will continue to limit dental implant procedure volumes to some degree, rising aesthetic consciousness and the increasing availability of low-cost products will support dental implant adoption, leading to sustained market&amp;nbsp;growth.​

	This Medtech 360 Report&amp;nbsp;provides key market metrics and high-level qualitative commentary for the dental implant&amp;nbsp;market&amp;nbsp;in Europe, including country-level data for major countries and aggregate data for the rest of Europe,&amp;nbsp;across a 10-year period.
</description><updateddate>2020/12/14</updateddate><pubdate>2020/12/16</pubdate><author>Swarnadip Dutta</author><report_nid>893774</report_nid></item></channel></rss>
